<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Day 2 on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>/en/day-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Day 2 on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/en/day-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 2 Session 4</title>
      <link>/en/day-2/session_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/day-2/session_4/</guid>
      <description>▶ Day 2 Session 3 Panel 1 NAME ROOM NUMBER 1 SPECIALIST GROUP NUMBER 1 Broken Telephone, No Connection: Misinformation and Missed Socio-Political Opportunities for Marginalised Zimbabwean Youth
Ms Nyasha Mutongwizo, Queensland University of Technology Framing the Otherness: Symbolic Power and Contention in Quebec Sovereignty Movement
Ms Ying Zheng, Tokyo University of Foreign Studies ▶ Day 2 Session 3 Panel 3 NAME ROOM NUMBER 3 SPECIALIST GROUP NUMBER 3 Multilingual Deliberation: A Problem in Need of Solving?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2 Session 5</title>
      <link>/en/day-2/session_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/day-2/session_5/</guid>
      <description>▶ Day 2 Session 6 Panel 1 NAME ROOM NUMBER 1 SPECIALIST GROUP NUMBER 1 The G20 and Russo-Ukrainian War: The Limitation of Rules in Responding to Contesting Values
Ms Diandra Ayu Larasati, Gadjah Mada University Ms Nasta Indraswari, Gadjah Mada University Ms Sitihatija Nurhuda Talaohu, Gadjah Mada University ▶ Day 2 Session 3 Panel 2 NAME ROOM NUMBER 2 SPECIALIST GROUP NUMBER 2 Future Imaginaries and Climate Deliberation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2 Session 6</title>
      <link>/en/day-2/session_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/day-2/session_6/</guid>
      <description>▶ Day 2 Session 4 Panel 1 NAME ROOM NUMBER 1 SPECIALIST GROUP NUMBER 1 Is the Kenyan 2022 Elections Free from Risk of Violence?
Ms Carol Mbeche, University of Johannesburg ▶ Day 2 Session 5 Panel 1 NAME ROOM NUMBER 1 SPECIALIST GROUP NUMBER 1 What’s populism got to do with it? The people, elites and ‘post-fascist’ discourse in the Italian far right’s 2022 election campaigns
Dr George Newth, University of Bath Young People&amp;rsquo;s Political Imaginaries: Discussing Climate Futures and Just Transformations</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
